Furqan Babar



furganbabarpk@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mrrajputpak



03006691987



https://mrrajputpak.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

Hi, It's Furgan. I am a Professional Website Designer.

I have been working with WordPress for 4 years and have developed a wide range of websites, from small personal blogs to large corporate websites. I am comfortable working with all aspects of WordPress, from installing and setting up a new site to customizing themes and plugins. I am also experienced in working with WooCommerce, the popular eCommerce platform that runs on top of WordPress. JavaScript:

I have been working with JavaScript for more than 1 year and have created many sites using JS. I am a professional MERN Stack developer at SJ Empower PVT LTD. If you are looking for someone to develop a website for you using JS, then I would be happy to help. Feel free to get in touch with me.

Experience



MERN Stack developer

SJ Empowers (Pvt) Ltd Nov 2022 - Present (3 months)



SJ Empowers (Pvt) Ltd Nov 2022 - Present (3 months)

Education



GC University Faisalabad

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications

Certified with WeLoveNoCode | No-code Tool: Wordpress - WeLoveNoCode 1673936319850x798859583202263000?red=1

Skills

Genesis Framework for WordPress • Wordpress Development • WordPress Design • Templates • PSD to Wordpress • WP • HTML5 • Content Management Systems (CMS) • Plugins • Front-End Development